{
    "question": "Tolong describe dengan tema \"my beloved home\"",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "I live in an ordinary house, but I always feel that I belong here for no reason. My house really cozy, it has 4 rooms with AC inside, 1 kitchen, 3 bathrooms, 1 livingrooms, and a green garden in front of it. My mom always take care of this house. I think it&#039;s right that our house is our palace because we can do what we want no matter what. Two years ago, I almost moved to the other house because there was an accident, and sssttt I can&#039;t tell you, because it&#039;s secret. So I think that&#039;s all",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "buat-text-hartatory-explenation-yang-berjudul-effect-of-insomni-716",
            "question": "Buat text hartatory explenation \u00a0yang berjudul effect of insomnia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Effect of Insomnia<br>Horatory -&gt; thesis -&gt; reason -&gt; suggestion<br><br>Insomnia is kind of illness that makes people hard to sleep. Due to its negative effect, this illness is categorized as the dangerous symptoms. The reason could be classified from Internal feelings of the person. Therefore if we have this illness, better to have consultation toward the doctor. We stand to benefit by the greater time of sleep that we have.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "sebutkan-kata-sifat-dari-pengelompokan-tersebut-sebanyak-banyak-851",
            "question": "Sebutkan kata sifat dari pengelompokan tersebut! (sebanyak-banyaknya)    menurut:1.Skin (Cool, Ho, ...)\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 2. Place (in,at,on,\u00a0...)\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 3. Age (New,old,\u00a0...)\r\n\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 4. Nose (sweet, smelling, ...)\r\n\r\nTolong kerjasamanya Friend's.. thanks so'much!",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Skin = cool, hot, soft, dirty, clean, rude, ugly, beautiful\nPlace : in, on, at, beside, behind, in front, between.\nAge : old, young, new,",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-expression-care-826",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan expression care",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "how poor you are<br>what a pity<br>i am sorry to hear that",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Situation : Your friend is sad.<br><br>Ana : <strong>Are you okay? You look so sad.</strong><br>Nia : <em>No, I&#039;m not okay.</em> I feel so sad because I had a fight with my brother yesterday.<br>Ana : Why?<br>Nia : He took my favorite novel without asking my permission and he ripped it! How can I not sad? He even not sorry at all and when I yelled at him, he yelled me back with his ridiculous reason that why should I got sad over a novel!<br>Ana : You must be really hurt...<br>Nia : Of couse I do.<br>Ana : <strong>What should I do to cheer you up?</strong><br>Nia : <em>Thanks for your attention</em> but no, sorry.<br>Ana : <strong>Really?</strong> I&#039;m sorry I can&#039;t help you much.<br>Nia: <em>Yeah, thanks</em>.<br><br><strong>bold: expressions<br></strong><em>italic: responses</em><strong><br></strong>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "berikan-5-kalimat-giving-instruction-312",
            "question": "Berikan 5 kalimat giving instruction",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "aku tulis dalam procedural text, how to make omelete<br>first,crack the eggs<br>after that beat the eggs<br>an then mix it with a salt or meat<br>after that cook it in a hot plate<br>finaly eat the eggs",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-jelasin-secara-singkat-conditional-sntence-type-3-trims-835",
            "question": "Tolong jelasin secara singkat \"Conditional Sntence\" Type 3 ,trims..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kalimat pengandaian untuk masa lalu dimana kalimatnya bertentangan<br>main clouse( s+ would/should+have+v3) if clouse( if+s+had+v3) jika if clouse tidak mempunyai kata kerja maka ditambah have been<br>contoh : he could have if his computer had not broken down",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Suatu kalimat pengandainya yang bertentangan dengan masa lalu.<br>Contohnya :<br>If you had said your guilty, I would have forgiven you<br>If + past perfect, S + would/should + have + past participle",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-text-spoof-pake-twist-falling-into-a-well-dong-306",
            "question": "Contoh text SPOOF pake twist \"falling into a well\" dong :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\nSpoof text: Falling Into a Well</span>\n<span>\n</span>\n\nThere was a man. When he was walking, he fell into a well.\n<span>\n<br></span>\n\nMany people saw the incident so they came to save him. Unfortunately no \none could enter the well to bring him out. Later, a smart man came up \nwith a bright idea to throw the man a strong rope to try to pull him out\n the well.\n<span>\n<br></span>\n\nWhen the rope reached\u00a0 and hit the man\u2019s head, he shouted angrily: \u201cDon&#039; bother me! Pick your own well, I am bathing.\u201d\n<br>\n\nDo you get the point why that short passage can be labeled as a spoof \ntext? Before we are going to go further, Let&#039;s see its rough translation\n to help you to\u00a0 get better understanding\n<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-simple-present-tense-verbal-dan-nominal-787",
            "question": "Contoh simple present tense, verbal dan nominal",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Simple Present Tense : Subject + V1 + keterangan waktu yang biasa dilakukan.ex : usually, every, always, often, sometimes,once, a week, a twice, etc.<br>Contohnya : he runs very quickly",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "coba-sebeutkan-contoh-dari-spoof-dan-kesimpulannya-845",
            "question": "Coba sebeutkan contoh dari spoof dan kesimpulannya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Contoh :<br>Joe&#039;s Mother got angry because her son got a low mark on English test.<br>\n\"Why did you get such a low mark on that test?\" Asked mother angrily. \nAsked by his angry mother, Joe just kept silent and went out.<br>\nA few moment, Joe came back home and met his mother again. His mother asked the same question.<br>\nJoe answered steadily, \"Because of absence.\"<br>\n\"You mean you were absent on the day of the test?\" Mother wondered.<br>\nJoe replied, \"No, but the kid who sits next to me was.\"\n\n<br><br>Kesimpulan :<br><span><span>sebuah teks yang berisi tentang humor meski sebagian teksnya \nsudah dimodifikasi dari aslinya.</span></span><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-dialog-dengan-menggunakan-ungkapan-expression-love-and-sa-467",
            "question": "Buatlah dialog dengan menggunakan ungkapan expression love and sadness beserta situasinya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\n<span>Me\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Mom, i should tell you right now</span></span>\n<br><span>\nMom : What is it\ndear ? tell me right now</span>\n<br><span>\n<span>Me\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : I should go to australia mom, i get that\nschollarship from school</span></span>\n<br><span>\nMom : Are you\nkidding me ?</span><br>\u00a0<span><span>Me\u00a0 : No mom, i\u2019m seriously this is a special\nchance for me to catch my dream would you like to </span></span>\n<span>\n<span>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 let me go ?</span></span><br>\u00a0<span><span>mom : But i\nlove you dear how can i let you go ?</span></span>\n<span>\n<span><br>me\u00a0\u00a0 : Calmdown mom everythings gonna be alright</span></span>\n<span>\n<span><br>mom : But ,\ni\u2019m afraid if i\u2019ll miss you my daughter i feel so sad\u00a0 if i let you go</span></span><br>\u00a0<span><span>me\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : It\u2019s ok mom, you can call me or message\nme distance is not a big problem</span></span><br>\u00a0<span>mom : If that\u2019s\nyou want i\u2019ll let you go, but you must take care there</span><br>\u00a0<span><span>me\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Sure mom\u00a0\nwish me luck</span></span> <span><br>mom : Sure dear</span><span><br><br></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "A : hy...<br>B : hy..<br>A : let&#039;s go to the cinema<br>B : what to do?<br>A : watching movies, now there recent a movie. you know?<br>B : really?? what the movie?<br>A : Harry Poter<br>B : really?? i love that movie. but.....<br>A : why??<br>B : i certainly shouldn&#039;t watch that movie<br>A : why?<br>B : now, i have a lot of tasks. so i will not go.<br>A : no problem. you can watch the next time<br>B : iam so sadness<br>A : be poison<br>B : thank you<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-the-word-darling-is-derived-from-an-old-english-term-meaning-251",
            "question": "1. The word \"Darling\" is derived from an old english term meaning \"Favorite Minion\" . Explain the positive and negative meaning of \"Darling\".    2. IBM is has laid of 20 percent of their workforce with a signature on a single piece of paper.\r\n\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 1\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 2\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 3\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 4\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 5\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 6\r\na. Find out the error option.\r\nb. Explain why it is wrong\r\n\r\nmohon bantuannya yaa..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. The word \"Darling\" is derived from an old English term meaning \"Favorite Minion\" . Explain the positive and negative meaning of \"Darling\".<br>Positive Meaning : It&#039;s a person that we concern as lovely and lovable, therefore we prioritize this darling as the first priority.<br>Negative : Since the word darling means favorite minion, it also trigger the feeling of possessiveness, that sometime it has negative effect on their freedom and privacy.\u00a0<br><br><span>2.\u00a0</span><u>IBM</u><span>\u00a0is\u00a0</span><u>has</u><span>\u00a0laid of\u00a0</span><u>20 percent</u><span>\u00a0of\u00a0</span><u>their</u>\u00a0<u>workforce</u><span>\u00a0with a signature on a\u00a0</span><u>single</u><span>\u00a0piece of paper.</span><br>\u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 1\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 2\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 3\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 4\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 5\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 6<br>a. Find out the error option.<br><br>number 2 - &gt; should be<br>IBM has laid without &#039;is&#039;\u00a0<br>b. Explain why it is wrong<br>if we use Is, then it will have pasive meaning, which means that IBM get bankrupt due to their worker\u00a0<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}